https://www.adexa.com/privacy-policy/

scroll
Contact Us1.833.ADEXAINCWorldwide Locations
Select LanguageChinese (Simplified)Chinese (Traditional)EnglishJapaneseKorean
Privacy PolicyHome
Privacy PolicyAdexa respects your privacy and we appreciate your interest in our firm.Security of your informationThe security of personal information is a high priority at Adexa. We maintain these web sites and all associated data with technical, administrative and physical safeguards to protect against loss, unauthorized access, destruction, misuse, modification and improper disclosure. No computer system or information can ever be fully protected against every possible hazard. But Adexa is committed to providing reasonable and appropriate security controls to protect our web sites and their information against foreseeable hazards.Information we collect and how it is usedWe collect aggregate information site-wide, including anonymous site stats. We also log domain names and/or IP addresses. On certain pages, we give users the option of providing us with contact information, including name, phone, and e-mail address, as a requirement for accessing our white paper documents. Providing this information is voluntary. We will NOT provide your information to any third party.On the Internet, a “cookie” is a piece of information (a file) that a Web site transfers to a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. The use of cookies is common on the Internet. We use cookies to determine if you have previously registered with our site and to provide you with access to our white papers.If you have opted into membership of our information newsletter, you may cancel participation in email newsletters by following the instructions on each newsletter.Information you provide may be used for Adexa marketing purposes, including but not limited to, one-off promotional e-mailing, direct mail, and sales contacts. We will honor all requests for list removal contact Adexa at 310-642-2100.Adexa reserves the right to change our privacy policy at any time and for any reason. For more information, please contact Adexa at 310-642-2100.
STAY CONNECTED WITH ADEXADon’t miss out on the latest innovations! Join our emailing list!
Email *
Contact UsAddress: Corporate Headquarters 5777 West Century Blvd. Suite 1100 Los Angeles, CA 90045Phone: (310) 642-2100Fax:
(310) 338-9878Email: info@adexa.comSolutionsSales and Operations Planning (S&OP)Sales & Operations Execution (S&OE)Supply Chain PlanningNetwork OptimizerInventory Planning Optimizer (MEIO)Factory Planning & SchedulingSupplier Visibility and PlanningAdexa GENIE© Predictive & Prescriptive AnalyticsServicesBusiness Solutions as a Service or B-SaaS©Adexa Implementation Methodology (AIM)Strategic Business ServicesDistributed CloudExpress Benchmark AnalysisAdexa Value AssessmentAbout UsExecutive TeamMission, Vision & ValuesInvestor RelationsCompany Fact SheetClientsPartnersCareers
Support
Request Demo
This website uses cookies to provide you with the best browsing experience.Find out more or adjust your settings.
Accept
Close GDPR Cookie Settings
Privacy Overview
Strictly Necessary Cookies
Privacy OverviewThis website uses cookies so that we can provide you with the best user experience possible. Cookie information is stored in your browser and performs functions such as recognizing you when you return to our website and helping our team to understand which sections of the website you find most interesting and useful. For more information, please review our Privacy Policy.
Strictly Necessary CookiesStrictly Necessary Cookie should be enabled at all times so that we can save your preferences for cookie settings.
Enable or Disable Cookies
If you disable this cookie, we will not be able to save your preferences. This means that every time you visit this website you will need to enable or disable cookies again.
Enable All
Save Changes
